A killer game of hide and seek.
Ready or Not is a horror, comedy film directed by Tyler Gillett.
A young bride's wedding night turns into her worst nightmare when her ridiculously
rich in-laws force her to play a gruesome game of hide-and-seek.
Grace MacCaulley, played by Samara Weaving.
Alex Le Domas, played by Mark O'Brien.
Daniel Le Domas, played by Adam Brody.
Tony Le Domas, played by Henry Czerny.
Becky Le Domas, played by Andie MacDowell.
Emilie Le Domas, played by Melanie Scrofano.
Ready or Not is a 2019 American comedy horror film directed by Matt
Bettinelli-Olpin and Tyler Gillett, and written by Guy Busick and R.
Christopher Murphy.
It stars Samara Weaving, Adam Brody, Mark O'Brien, Elyse Levesque,
Nicky Guadagni, Henry Czerny and Andie MacDowell.
It follows a young bride who is hunted by her spouse's wealthy family
as part of a wedding night ritual to worship the Devil.
Preparations began in November 2017 when Bettinelli-Olpin and Gillett, members of the filmmaking collective
Radio Silence, were hired as directors, with Busick and Murphy attached to write the screenplay.
After setting an initial release date, casting
occurred from August to October 2018.
Principal photography began later that month and concluded in November, in
locations in and around Toronto, Canada and the surrounding Ontario area.
Brian Tyler was hired to compose and conduct the film's score, marking
his first collaboration with Bettinelli-Olpin and Gillett.
Ready or Not premiered at the Fantasia International Film Festival on July 27, 2019, and was
theatrically released in the United States on August 21, 2019, by Searchlight Pictures.
It received positive reviews from critics and grossed $57.6
million worldwide against a $6 million budget.
It was nominated for Best Horror Film at the 46th Saturn Awards.
A sequel, Ready or Not 2: Here I Come, is
scheduled to be released in March 2026.
The film explores themes of escape, ritual, marriage, satanism, gore.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.